<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EveryDayHabit</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="action_reset">Reset</string>
    <string name="action_new_habit">New Habit</string>
    <string name="action_startup_info">Info</string>

    <string name="button_2_text">Reset</string>

    <string name="edit_day_activity_title">Habit Progress Report</string>
    <string name="edit_day_default">Did you have a successful day?</string>
    <string name="edit_day_did_you">"Did you "</string>
    <string name="edit_day_today">" today?"</string>
    <string name="edit_day_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="edit_day_no">No</string>
    <string name="edit_day_why">Why were you unsuccessful?</string>
    <string name="edit_day_comments">Comments:</string>
    <string name="edit_day_reason">Log your reason</string>
    <string name="edit_day_log_comment">Log your comments</string>
    <string name="edit_day_legit">My reason is actually legit</string>
    <string name="edit_day_button">Done</string>

    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id">ca-app-pub-5782047288878600/6628122771</string>

    <string name="new_habit_activity_title">New Habit</string>
    <string name="new_habit_1">Let\'s start a new habit!\n
        \nGood habits serve to create routine, order and efficiency and bad habits can lock us into
        negative patterns of behaviour.\n
        \nMaking or breaking a habit takes conscious mental effort and perseverance, but the
        pay off can be massive. Think what it is that you want to achieve, reduce it to the
        simplest possible daily activity that would take very little time and physical effort to
        complete. Now think of something in your daily routine that can act as a trigger for
        performing your new habit and complete the following:\n
    </string>
    <string name="new_habit_2">Every day, I am going to…\n</string>
    <string name="new_habit_notify_title">Notification Time</string>
    <string name="new_habit_notify">Set a daily reminder to log your progress.
        (Don\'t rely on this as a trigger to perform your habit)\n</string>
    <string name="new_habit_start_today">I\'m starting today</string>
    <string name="new_habit_start_tomorrow">I can only start tomorrow</string>
    <string name="new_habit_prompt">Enter simple daily action</string>
    <string name="new_habit_button">Add Habit</string>

    <string name="delete_habit">Delete Habit</string>

    <string name="preference_category_general">General Settings</string>
    <string name="preference_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="preference_category_specific">Habit Settings</string>
    <string name="preference_accept_excuses">Accept Legitimate Excuses</string>
    <string name="preference_excuses_summary_on">Legitimate excuses will not break streaks</string>
    <string name="preference_excuses_summary_off">Legitimate excuses are considered missed days
        and will break streaks</string>

    <string name="default_habit_text">Default Habit Text</string>
    <string name="default_habit_word">Habit</string>
    <string name="preference_notification_tone">Notification Tone</string>

    <string name="txt_habit">Habit</string>
    <string name="txt_new_habit">New Habit</string>
    <string name="txt_add_new_habit">Add New Habit</string>
    <string name="txt_no_reason">You didn\'t log a reason</string>
    <string name="txt_no_log">No progress logged</string>

    <string name="first_use_activity_title">EveryDayHabit</string>
    <string name="first_use_button">Let\'s Get Started</string>
    <string name="first_use_text">Welcome to EveryDayHabit.\n
        \nHabits are powerful mini auto-pilot scripts that kick in with very specific triggers.
        They free up our mental capacity by essentially removing the need to make active decisions
        or to respond to stimuli while the habit script is running. Habits are not only executed
        automatically, but are also formed automatically, with our brains constantly searching for
        behavioural patterns to automate in order to optimise our day to day lives.
        This might make habits hard to break, but luckily makes it fairly straight forward
        to form new positive habits.\n

        \nTo achieve your ultimate goal will require effort and perseverance, but to establish a
        relevant micro habit to get you started does not. By breaking the steps down into the
        simplest possible daily activity that would take very little time and physical effort to
        complete, habit formation is a walk in the park.\n

        \nEvery habit starts with a trigger. The easiest way to approach the formation of a new
        habit is to piggyback it on another habitual daily activity.
        Another option is to use the trigger of a bad habit you want to drop and substitute your
        new positive habit. If you do this, make sure that the new habit has a similar <i>reward</i>
        to the bad habit you are replacing.\n

        \nWith EveryDayHabit there are also no Mondays and no first-of-the-months,
        only the very next day. Your habit starts right now.\n

        \nThere are many great resources out there on habit formation and the powerful impact
        habits have on our lives, but these are the basics you need to get started. Make it simple,
        keep the trigger and reward consistent, and do it every day!
    </string>

    <string name="congratulations_activity_title">Congratulations!</string>
    <string name="congratulations_text">
        Well done on completing seven weeks of your habit to %1$s every day!\n
        \nYou maintained a success rate of %2$s, and had a best running streak of %3$s.\n
        \nWhile 49 straight days should be sufficient to establish your habit, you\'re welcome to
        keep tracking your activity with EveryDayHabit. We\'ll shift your grid to display the most
        recent seven weeks only, but your stats will still be based on your progress since day one.
    </string>
    <string name="congratulations_button">Got It</string>
    <string name="action_rate">Rate App</string>


</resources>
